siteuptime.com 2016-03-06

# SiteUptime - Website and Server Monitoring Service

This privacy policy sets out how SiteUptime LLC uses and protects any information that you provide to us when using our service. We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by our users. We have adopted this privacy policy to assure our users that their personal information will be kept confidential. 

### Your Information

  * When registering for a SiteUptime LLC account, we ask for your name, email address, billing address, payment information (credit card/PayPal). Users who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card or Paypal account information.
  * When using your SiteUptime LLC account you may be asked for your domain name, website address, URL, hostname, IP address, etc.
  * SiteUptime LLC uses the information we collect to provision services, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement and to contact our users.
  * The information you provide to SiteUptime LLC is never sold or made available to others.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### Cookies

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * SiteUptime LLC occasionally uses "cookies", which allows us to recognize who you are at subsequent visits to our site and to your member control panel. You can change your browser settings to accept or reject cookies.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.  

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Our privacy agreement may change from time to time, any major change will be announced via email. 

If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact us.
